907 Forest Drive, Garner, NC 27529 (919) 921-7562 massengillashley@icloud.com ashleymassengill.github.io

ashlevmassengill.com

OVERVIEW

Through my experiences, I have learned where my strengths lie. I enjoy writing code and turning designs into interactive products through HTML and CSS. My goal is to continue growing my experience and knowledge in ways that allow me to tap into the creative and organized sides of my personality to create a product that is the best outcome for everyone.

STRENGTHS

★ Creative Thinking

★ Great Eye for Detail ★ Analytical Thinking

★ Extreme Efficiency

★ Teaching Skills

★ Organization

WORK HISTORY

Front-End Developer, Coalmarch

Apr 2016 - Dec 2018
Raleigh, NC

- Built and styled custom designed enterprise client sites on Drupal7
- Developed proprietary features and templates for Drupal7 based Sprowt website platform.
- Lead front-end developer and product owner on Teambuilder, Coalmarch.com.
- Team organization lead including documentation, Pantheon maintenance.

1 Apr 2016 - Jul 2016 (\$) Raleigh, NC Database Manager, RCI, Inc.

- Managed internal tech support including computer hardware, software, phone systems, servers, and website.
- Guided implementation of new AMS through search, demon, contract, setup and testing phases into training and go-live.
- Created and maintained all reporting operations for each department.

1 Dec 2010 - Apr 2016 \$ Raleigh, NC Meetings Specialist, RCI, Inc.

- Produced event based website layouts and coding.
- Managed all event registrations for 10+ attendee events to 1500+ attedee events.
- Created all meeting collateral for international events from general education to conventions and trade shows.

VOLUNTEER HISTORY

Guest Services NC State Athletics

🗓 Aug 2016 - current 🜎 Raleigh, NC

Box Office & Boutique Assistant Carolina Ballet

🗓 Aug 2010 - current 🜎 Raleigh, NC

Admissions & Ticketing Services USGA Men's & Women's US Open

🗓 Jul 2014 (\$) Pinehurst, NC

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5 advanced

CSS3 advanced

Sass advanced

AngularJS beginner

PHP intermediate

Git intermediate

Drupal7 advanced

Drupal8 beginner

Pantheon advanced

Jira advanced

Atom advanced

Adobe Illustrator intermediate

Adobe Photoshop intermediate

Adobe InDesign intermediate

Adobe Acrobat advanced

InVision Intermediate

Crystal Reports intermediate

Apple iWork advanced

Microsoft Office advanced

G Suite advanced

EDUCATION

UI Design, The Iron Yard

1 Oct 2016 - Jan 2017 \$ Raleigh, NC

East Carolina University

🗓 Aug 2001 - May 2003 💲 Greenville, NC

AFFILIATIONS

Women Who Code Raleigh/Durham

AIGA Raleigh

Triangle UXPA